lowendmac.com 2008-06-23

# Low End Mac Privacy Policy

## Low End Mac's Privacy Policy

International privacy standards require businesses to:

  * notify consumers what they do with personal data such as names and email addresses
  * use the information only for its stated purpose
  * allow consumers to examine and correct data collected about them
  * give them a choice to forbid sharing that information for marketing purposes
  * store the data in a secure manner
  * provide recourse for consumers whose privacy has been violated

Low End Mac does not collect personally identifiable information about visitors unless they specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis, such as subscribing to one of our email lists. In the case of email lists, only the list managers have access to these email addresses.

We cannot protect the identity or email address of those who post to our email lists, since these lists are archived on the Web and available for anyone to peruse. We do what we can to prevent spammers from harvesting email addresses from the archives, but we cannot guarantee that the list archives will not be spidered for email addresses. By posting to any of our lists, you take the risk that your email address will be accessible to spammers. We sincerely wish it weren't so, do what we can to prevent it, but can't promise that some incorrigible lowlife spammer won't get your address.

Our site logs track IP addresses, as well as the browser and operating system used by visitors. This information is used for statistical purposes only.

We do not use any type of cookies on Low End Mac, although BackBeat Media (which handles our display ads) and advertisers may use cookies and track additional information for their own purposes. This information is collected and maintained by these organizations under their own privacy policies, which may be different from Low End Mac's policy.

Dan Knight , publisher, Low End Mac 

### Low End Mac Reader Specials

[ **Memory To Go Special:**](http://www.memorytogo.com/?rfr=lowendmac) MacPro 8 Core Memory 4GB kit $192 / 2GB kit $109. MacBook Pro / MacMini / iMac Intel Core2 DUO 2GB $44 1GB $23--Free shipping available.

[ **Download Typestyler,**](http://adserver1.backbeatmedia.com/servlet/ajrotator/270/662/clickHTML?ajkey=D3FC04ACCF3A96D6D1EAAB2400001BAC00001B2200000CEB00001B6AFFFFFF91FFFFFF91FFFFFFFF1A21F7F3) still the Ultimate Styling Tool for Internet, Print and Video Graphics. Works great in Classic with a Native OS X Version on the way. [Free Tryout: www.typestyler.com](http://adserver1.backbeatmedia.com/servlet/ajrotator/270/662/clickHTML?ajkey=D3FC04ACCF3A96D6D1EAAB2400001BAC00001B2200000CEB00001B6AFFFFFF91FFFFFF91FFFFFFFF1A21F7F3)

[ ](http://adserver1.backbeatmedia.com/servlet/ajrotator/270/229/clickHTML?ajkey=4D63E9F9CF3A96D6D1EAAB24000021150000288200001A5700001B6AFFFFFF91FFFFFF91FFFFFFFFFD842C8A) **[LA Computer Company:](http://adserver1.backbeatmedia.com/servlet/ajrotator/270/229/clickHTML?ajkey=4D63E9F9CF3A96D6D1EAAB24000021150000288200001A5700001B6AFFFFFF91FFFFFF91FFFFFFFFFD842C8A)** LA Computer Company: Specials on AppleCare, Apple Displays, MacBooks, iMac's, MacBook Pros, Laptop and iPod accessories and more. Apple A/C Adapters for laptops starting at $25.00 Call 1-800-941-7654 or [Click Here. ](http://adserver1.backbeatmedia.com/servlet/ajrotator/270/229/clickHTML?ajkey=4D63E9F9CF3A96D6D1EAAB24000021150000288200001A5700001B6AFFFFFF91FFFFFF91FFFFFFFFFD842C8A)

[**Other World Computing**](http://adserver1.backbeatmedia.com/servlet/ajrotator/270/864/clickHTML?ajkey=A42FDF14CF3A96D6D1EAAB2400001EBA00001EC400001A5800001B6AFFFFFF91FFFFFF91FFFFFFFF07D569FE) has the Upgrades, Enhancements, and Accessories for getting the most from your Mac. Quality Products, Competitive Prices, Expert Support Staff - [www.macsales.com](http://adserver1.backbeatmedia.com/servlet/ajrotator/270/864/clickHTML?ajkey=A42FDF14CF3A96D6D1EAAB2400001EBA00001EC400001A5800001B6AFFFFFF91FFFFFF91FFFFFFFF07D569FE)

Mac users can finally play [Party Poker for Mac](http://www.imaconlinepoker.com/mac/online/poker/party-poker/). Not only that, they can also learn how to play [PokerStars for Mac](http://www.imaconlinepoker.com/mac/online/poker/pokerstars/).

[](http://adserver1.backbeatmedia.com/servlet/ajrotator/270/706/clickHTML?ajkey=DF6D3D41CF3A96D6D1EAAB24000035DF000035DC00001EC800001B6AFFFFFF91FFFFFF91FFFFFFFF19063B6B) Laptop Hardware Provided by [TechRestore](http://adserver1.backbeatmedia.com/servlet/ajrotator/270/706/clickHTML?ajkey=DF6D3D41CF3A96D6D1EAAB24000035DF000035DC00001EC800001B6AFFFFFF91FFFFFF91FFFFFFFF19063B6B) \- Overnight Mac & iPod Repairs.

Compare products like [desktop computers](http://www.ciao.com/Desktops_10000034_2 "Desktop Reviews"), [laptops](http://www.ciao.com/Laptops_10000035_2 "Laptop reviews"), and [LCD TVs ](http://www.ciao.com/LCD_Monitors_10000037_2 "LCD Monitor comparison") side by side! All the information and reviews to make the best purchasing decision for a new cell phone [GPS products](http://www.ciao.com/GPS_Systems_10000169_2 "GPS Reviews and Price Comparison") or [MP3 players](http://www.ciao.com/MP3_Players_10000127_3 "Compare MP3 Player"). [The Ciao network](http://www.ciao.com/ "For reviews and price comparison") makes searching products easy for you.

[](http://adserver1.backbeatmedia.com/servlet/ajrotator/270/260/clickHTML?ajkey=B0A14A93CF3A96D6D1EAAB2400003CF50000391C0000391B00001B6AFFFFFF91FFFFFF91FFFFFFFF02F5F5EC)[](http://adserver1.backbeatmedia.com/servlet/ajrotator/270/260/clickHTML?ajkey=B0A14A93CF3A96D6D1EAAB2400003CF50000391C0000391B00001B6AFFFFFF91FFFFFF91FFFFFFFF02F5F5EC) MacBook/MacBook Pro / MacMini / iMac Intel Core2 DUO DDR2 667Mhz 4GB Kit $84, 3GB Kit $60, 2GB Kit $40 1GB $20. [ Click to Maximize your Macs...](http://adserver1.backbeatmedia.com/servlet/ajrotator/270/260/clickHTML?ajkey=B0A14A93CF3A96D6D1EAAB2400003CF50000391C0000391B00001B6AFFFFFF91FFFFFF91FFFFFFFF02F5F5EC)

Entire Low End Mac website copyright ©1997-2008 by Cobweb Publishing, Inc., unless otherwise noted. All rights reserved. Advice presented in good faith, but what works for one may not work for all. Please report errors to [webmaster](mailto:lowendmac@gmail.com) .  
  LINKS: We allow and encourage links to any public page as long as the linked page does not appear within a frame that prevents bookmarking it.  
  Access our RSS news feed at http://lowendmac.com/feed.xml.  
  Email may be published at our discretion; email addresses will not be published without permission, and we will encrypt them in hopes of avoiding spammers. If you prefer your message not be published, mark it "not for publication." Letters may be edited for length, context, and to match house style.  
  PRIVACY: We don't collect personal information unless you explicitly provide it. For more details, see our Terms of Use.  
  Low End Mac is an independent publication and has not been authorized, sponsored, or otherwise approved by Apple Inc. Apple, the Apple logo, Macintosh, iBook, iMac, eMac, iPod, PowerBook, MacBook, Mac Pro, Apple TV, and AirPort are [registered trademarks of Apple Inc.](http://www.apple.com/legal/trademark/) Additional company and product names may be trademarks or registered trademarks and are hereby acknowledged.  | 
* Mac of the Day: Power Mac G5, June 2003 - IBM's PowerPC 970 at 1.6-2.0 GHz, HyperTransport archictecture, serial ATA, PCI-X, and AirPort Extreme.
* List of the Day: [Mac-N-DOS](http://lowendmac.com/lists/macndos.shtml) is for those who use Windows and the Mac OS.  

 **Channels**  
 Power Macs  
 iMac Channel  
 iBook/PowerBook  
 MacInSchool  
**Computer Profiles**  
 iMac  
 Power Mac  
 PowerBook/iBook  
 Performas  
 Mac Clones  
 Older Macs  
 Lisa • NeXT  
**Editorial Archive**  
**Mac Daniel's Advice**  
**Email Lists**  
[**LEMchat**](aim:gochat?roomname=LEMchat) (uses AIM)  
**Online Tech Journal**  
**Consumer**  
 advice, reviews  
 guides, deals  
**Software**  
**Apple History**  
**Best of the Web**  
 Best of the Mac Web surveys  
**Miscellaneous Links  
**  Best Used Mac Buys  
 Used Mac Dealers  
 Video Cards  
 Mac OS X  
 Mac Linux  
 Macspeak  
 RAM Upgrades  
**About Low End Mac**  
**Site Contacts**

### Support LEM

#### Affiliates

Our advertising is handled by [BackBeat Media](http://www.backbeatmedia.com/). For detailed price quotes and advertising information, please contact[Greg Snyder](mailto:lem@backbeatmedia.com)at BackBeat Media (646-546-5194). This number is for advertising only.
